{
    "subject": "Archduchess_Elisabeth_Franziska_of_Austria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Archduke_Ferdinand_Karl_Viktor_of_Austria-Este",
    "human_readable": "Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria is married to Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872462749481201,
            "question": "Who is Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9251481890678406,
            "question": "Where did Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska and Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9236680269241333,
            "question": "What is the full name of Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9190362095832825,
            "question": "What is the nature of the relationship between Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska and Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.918430507183075,
            "question": "Is Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska related to any other Austrian royalty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8734425902366638,
            "question": "What were the social circles of Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska and Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7680121660232544,
            "question": "Do Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska and Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor have any children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7230899333953857,
            "question": "To which royal family does Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6580103635787964,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2671167850494385,
            "question": "Were there any notable events associated with their marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria is married to Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este.",
            "html": "yago_24997_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor?",
            "html": "yago_24997_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which royal family does Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor belong?",
            "html": "yago_24997_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska and Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor have any children?",
            "html": "yago_24997_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24997_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria and Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este. Specifically, it states:\n\n\"MarriageArchduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este\nWedding: 4.10.1847 in Sch\u00f6nbrunn Palace, Vienna\n\nArchduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria\n(* 17.1.1831, O 4.10.1847, O 18.4.1854, \u2020 14.2.1903)\"\n\nThis confirms that Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria was married to Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este on October 4, 1847."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}